

#### Contact



**+34 600 97 38 36** 



emtuero@hotmail.com



manumaldonado.com



്ര്ര emanuel-mt



ManuuMT

#### About me

Hello, I'm Manu!

I'm 26 years old. I was born in Argentina and I've been living in Spain since 2018.

I spent the last 11 years working in customer service, but in 2021 I decided to quit my job and change my life, making programming my full time job.

#### Skill set



































## Soft skills

- · Problem solver
- Creative
- Fast learner
- · Self-educated
- · Committed and liable
- · Great communicator and team player

#### Languages

· Spanish: native · English: B2

# **EMANUEL MALDONADO**

### Full Stack Developer

### Work experience

#### Worksut - CMO y Co-Founder

December 2021 - present // Remote

· Startup focused on revolutionizing the way of finding job and hiring people in the 21st century.

#### Panko Escalopería - Manager

September 2019 - October 2021 // Palma de Mallorca, Spain

- · Waiter and restaurant manager
- · Administrative tasks, cash, sales, and customer service.

#### **Burger King - Customer service**

Februaty 2018- October 2018 // Palma de Mallorca, Spain

- · Customer service mainly oriented to english speakers that walked through the Son Sant Joan International Airport (PMI).
- · Cleaning tasks, product organization, sails, inventary and stock control.

#### **Education**

#### 4Geeks Academy Bootcamp - Full Stack Developer

October 2021 - February 2022 // Remote

- · Web design with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, & Bootstrap.
- · Frontend development with React (Flux + Hooks).
- Backend development with Python (Flask + SQLAlchemy).
- · API's and relational data bases creation, version control with GIT, Node package management.

#### School of Technical Secondary Education n°5 -**IT Technician**

March 2008 - December 2014 // Mar del Plata, Argentina

- · High school finished.
- · 7 years of IT and electronic workshops.
- Equivalent to an IT "Medium degree FP" in Spain.

# **Projects**

#### Guardian - Idea & Full Stack Development

Web application created by the need to make the streets safer for residents and tourists from different cities around the world.